Guide to the SPURS National Honor Society Records1922-2006
Montana State University Library, Archives and Special Collections, Manuscript Collections
SPURS National Honor Society records
1922-2006
Montana State University Library, Archives and Special Collections, Manuscript Collections
SPURS National Honor Society
MSU.72042
Accession 72042
19 linear feet
The SPURS National Honor Society Records comprise multiple accessions donated to Special Collections over the course of several years. The Materials have been arranged into five series: Scrapbooks, Ephemera, Local Records, National Records, and Audio and Photographic Materials.
Spurs (Service, Patriotism, Unity, Responsibility, and Sacrifice) National Honor Society was a women's collegiate sophomore honor society founded at Montana State University - Bozeman, February 14, 1922. The founding purpose of the Spurs was to serve the college or university and the community, to support the activities in which the student body participates, to further among the women students a spirit of loyalty and helpfulness, and to uphold the traditions of the college or university.
Originally a women-only organization, Spurs went co-educational in 1976. Chapters were spread across the United States, primarily at smaller colleges and universities and emphasis remained on community service and scholarship.
The Spurs dissolved as a national organization as of May 31, 2006 by decision of the October 2005 National Convention. However, the MSU Spurs that were left decided to join with the MSU Student Alumni Association the following the year.
The SPURS National Honor Society Records are a compilation of items collected from multiple donors over multiple years. The items cover activities for the local (original) chapter at Montana State University, the national organization, and from chapters across the country. They cover the span of time between 1926 and 2006, which is very close to the entire lifespan of the organization (1922-2006). The collection is an example of club activities, promotional materials for MSU and the SPURS club, Honor Society history, and the history of the MSU Alumni Association since the SPURS joined with the Alumni Association after SPURS was dissolved.
Series 1 Scrapbooks Series 2 Ephemera Series 3 Local Records Series 4 National Records Series 5 Audio and Photographic Materials
This collection is open for research.
The records of the Spurs comprise accession numbers 2671, 72042, 76025, 77045, 81040, 82017, 85012, 85103, 88022, 89043, 90027, 90062, 91015, 91019, 92045, 93013, and 95008. Accession 90062 was donated by Marge Paisley. A portion of accession 93013 was donated by Marguerite Fulkner. Accession 95008 was donated by Brenda Lorang. Accession 83038x was added April 18, 2014. Accession 2671 was donated by Sharron Starling in 2020 and added to the collection September 14, 2022
Montana State College--Students--Societies, etc.; SPURS National Honor Society--Archives; Montana State College
Montana--Bozeman; United States, West
College students--Montana--Bozeman--Societies, etc.; Women college students--Montana--Bozeman--Societies, etc.; Students--West (U.S.)--Societies, etc.; Women college students--West (U.S.)--Societies, etc.; College students--Societies, etc.; Students--Societies, etc.; Women college students--Societies, etc.
Colleges and Universities; Clubs and Societies; Elementary and Secondary Education; Women; Montana; Bozeman
Archives
- Scrapbooks, 1
  The scrapbooks in this series were created or collected by the Montana Spurs. The scrapbooks contain clippings, photographs, notes, ephemera, etc. retained by the group to commemorate their history.
  - MSC Spurs, 1926-1927 (Box 1)
  - MSC Spurs, 1959-1960 (Box 1)
  - MSC Spurs, 1931-1950 (Box 2)
  - MSC Spurs, 1953-1957 (Box 3)
  - MSC Spurs, 1958-1959 (Box 4)
  - MSC Spurs, 1961-1962
  - MSC Spurs, 1962-1963
  - MSC Spurs, 1964-1965 (Box 5)
  - MSC Spurs, 1965-1966 (Box 6)
  - MSC Spurs, 1966-1967
  - MSC Spurs, 1967-1968 (Box 7)
  - MSC Spurs, 1968-1969
  - MSC Spurs, 1969-1970 (Box 8)
  - MSC Spurs, 1972-1973
  - MSC Spurs, 1971-1972
  - Spur National Convention, 1972
  - MSC Spurs, 1970-1971 (Box 9)
  - MSC Spurs, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - MSC Spurs, 1974-1975 (Box 11)
  - MSC Spurs, 1975-1976 (Box 12)
  - MSC Spurs, 1976-1977 (Box 13)
  - MSC Spurs, 1977-1978 (Box 14)
  - MSC Spurs, 1978-1979
  - MSC Spurs, 1980-1981 (Box 15)
  - MSC Spurs, 1981-1982 (Box 16)
  - MSC Spurs, 1983-1984 (Box 17)
  - MSC Spurs, 1987-1988
  - MSC Spurs, 1990-1991
  - MSC Spurs, 1988-1989 (Box 18)
  - MSC Spurs, 1989-1990 (Box 19)
  - MSC Spurs, 1982-1983
  - Spurs California State College at Long Beach, 1963-1964 (Box 20)
  - Spurs California State College at Long Beach, 1964-1965
  - Spurs Cal-State Long Beach, 1965-1966
  - A Spur History from Carroll College, Helena, Montana, 1984-1985 (Box 21)
  - National Spurs, 1982-1984
  - Chapter Histories, Regions 1-3, 1891-1972 (Box 22)
  - Chapter Histories Regions 4-11, 1925-1975
  - MSC Spurs Histories, 1941-1943
  - MSU Spurs, 50 year reunion, classes, 1903-1930 (Box-folder 22A)
  - MSU Spurs, 50 year reunion, classes, 1931-1937
- Ephemera, 2
  Materials in this series consist of items owned/used by members throughout their membership within the organization. They consist of Spurs branded clothing items, membership pins, embroidered patches, decorative embroidered pillows, boot spurs, member award plaques and certificates, a rubber stamp, presidential gavel, a brass tankard, and documentation items including: song books, newspaper clippings, convention guest books, chapter charters (Long Beach State College, and University of Nevada at Las Vegas), and personal remembrances. The song books contain lyrics for chapter specific songs, SPURS National songs, and "fun songs" (public domain songs, and chorus songs) to be used at events and meetings. Some song books include music notation in addition to lyrics. Award plaques include award winner names, and some items have the owner name engraved/stitched into them.
  - Spurs Sweatshirt, Donated by Marguerite Fulber, School Year, 1961-1962 (Box 23)
  - White Spurs Sweater, Donated by K. Stephens
  - Blue Spurs Sweater, Donated by L. Hughes
  - Blue Skirt
  - Blue North Dakota Spurs Short-Sleeve Shirt
  - Yellow International Spurs Polo Shirt
  - Blue and Gold Spur Pillow, 1937
  - Blue and Yellow Beanie, 1994
  - Blue, Green, and Gold Beanie, 1977
  - International Spurs, Region VIII European Brass Tankard
  - MSU Spurs President Gavel
  - Cream MSU Spurs and Fangs Long Sleeve Shirt, 1983-1984
  - Cream MSC Fangs Cardigan
  - Cream Spurs Sweater
  - Treasurer Pin (Box 24)
  - Historian's Double Book Pin
  - Editor's Book Pin
  - Advisor's Block A Pin
  - Gold Megaphone Pin
  - Gold Rectangle Etched with 'IV' Pin
  - Silver Spur With Inlaid Blue Stones Pin
  - Spurs National Honor Society Pin
  - Spur Stamp
  - National Convention Guest Book, 1968
  - National Convention Guest Book, 1972
  - The International Spurs, Gail Hanninnen Plaque, 1989-1995
  - The National Spurs Martha Pearl "Teach" Jones Award, 1966-1996
  - Newspaper Clippings, circa 1965-1972 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Spur Patches (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Small Embroidered Blue and Gold Spur on White Background with Gold Edging
    - Small Embroidered Blue and Gold Spur on White Background with Gold Edging, "REG. DIR. VII", with Gold, White Pearl Inset, Spur Pin and VII Pin
    - Small Embroidered Blue Gold Spur on White Background with Gold Edging," EX. SEC-TREAS.", with Gold, White Pearl Inset, Spur Pin and Secretary-Treasurer Pin
    - Small Embroidered Blue and Gold on Blue Background with Gold Edging, "REG. DIR. X"
    - Medium Embroidered Blue and Gold Spur on Blue Background with Gold Edging, "Senior Advisor"
    - Medium Embroidered Blue and Gold Spur On Blue Background with Gold Edging, "EXEC. SEC. TREAS."
    - Medium Blue Stitched Gold Spur on Blue Background
    - Medium Gold and Blue Stitched Gold Spur on Blue Background, "National Spurs Secretary Treasurer"
    - Medium Burgundy Stitched White Spur on Burgundy Background
    - Large Embroidered Blue and Gold Spur on Blue Background with Gold Edging
    - Large Blue Stitched Gold Spur on Blue Background, with Gold Spur Pin
    - Small Embroidered Blue and Gold Spur on Blue Background with Gold Edging, with Gold Spur Pin, and Torch Pin
  - Spur Thoughts, by Becky (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Long Beach State College Charter (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - University of Nevada at Las Vegas Charter (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - National Spurs Certificate of Honorary Membership, Dr. Gladys Roehm (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Sing All Men (Box 25)
  - 112 Familiar Hymns and Gospel Songs
  - Women's Get-together Songs
  - The National Spurs, Margie Paisley
  - The National Spurs, RD III
  - Spur Songs (Box 25, Folder 1-4)
  - Golden Anniversary Spurs (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Spur Songbook, MSU Spurs, 1978-1979 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Boot Spurs, 45 individual Boot Spurs: items range from small to large. Some items still have their tooled boot leather attachments, some have plain leather attachments, a few have metal attachments, and many have no attachments at all. Two spurs are preserved in plastic, zip-lock bags and are labeled "Mountain Man" and "Sage Brushers", while the rest are preserved in brown paper. Original numbering has been preserved when availble. Items are numbered 001-043 as some numbers have an item "a" and "b". Als0, there is an item 014b (orignal numbering) but no item 014a. (Box 26, Object 021b and 022, Object 039, 040, 041, 042, and 043)
  - SPUR of the Month, November, Sharron Henriques, Plaque (Box 24)
  - SPUR of the Year, 1985, Sharron Henriques, Plaque (Box 24)
  - Blue and Yellow Spur Polo Shirt, 1984-1985 (Box 45)
  - White and Blue Spurs and Fangs Polo Shirt, 1984-1985 (Box 45)
  - White and Yellow, Square, Needlepoint Spurs Pillow, 1984-1985 (Box 45)
  - White, Round, Needlepoint Spurs Pillow, 1984-1985 (Box 45)
  - White, Cotton, Spurs Handkerchief for Sharron (Box 45)
- Local Records, 3
  Materials in this series pertain to the local Montana State University chapter of the Spurs. Records include minutes, reports, membership lists, and correspondence.
  - Local Minutes, 1936-1939 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Local Minutes, 1939-1941 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Local Minutes, 1942-1943 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Local Minutes, 1943-1946 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Local Minutes, 1946-1948 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Local Minutes, 1949-1951 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Local Minutes, 1934-1959 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Local Minutes, 1959-1964 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Local Minutes, 1964-1974 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Local Minutes, 1974-1978 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Local Minutes, 1978-1982 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Local Minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Local Minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Local Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Local Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Local Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Convention Reports, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Convention Reports, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Convention Reports, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Convention Reports, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Convention Reports, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Convention Reports, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Orientation Week Reports, 1960-1977 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Favorite Sayings and Traditions (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Spur-O-Gram, February 1968-December 1969 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Spur-O-Gram, 1970-1972 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous Publications (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Activity Reports, 1959-1968 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Activity Reports, 1968-1971 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Committee Report-Advisors (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Committee Report-Beanie Dance (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Committee Report-By-Laws (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Committee Report-Calling Committee (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Committee Report-Cat Griz Relations (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Committee Report-Church (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Committee Report-Founder's Day (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Committee Report-High School Week (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Committee Report-Homecoming (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Committee Report-M-Day Procedures (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Committee Report-Miscellaneous, 1957-1983 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Committee Report-Money Making Projects (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Committee Report-National Officer Visits (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Committee Report-Parties (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Committee Report-Projects (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Committee Report-Regional Convention (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Committee Report-Spur Of The Year Awards (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Committee Report-Toy Drive (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Committee Report-Uniforms (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Treasurer Report, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Treasurer Report, 1972-1974 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Vice President Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Guidelines and Historical Information (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Speeches, 1962-1974 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Spur Test (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Visitation Evaluations, 1961-1969 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Selections, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Spur Alumnae List (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Spur Officers List (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Spur Committee Members List (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 52)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 28, Folder 53)
  - National Awards (Box 28, Folder 54)
  - Spur Education (Box 28, Folder 55)
  - Thank You's (Box 28, Folder 56)
  - 50 Years MSU Spurs Members List through, 1972 (Box 29)
  - Executive Secretary Treasurer, Mary Lou McCallum, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 29A/1)
  - Spur Orientation, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 29A/2)
  - Freshman Program, 1958-1984 (Box-folder 29A/3)
  - Junior Advisor (Box-folder 29A/4)
  - Traditions and Old By-laws, 1969-1982 (Box-folder 29A/5)
  - Constitution, 1963-1975 (Box-folder 29A/6)
  - Correspondence, 1923-1971 (Box-folder 29A/7)
  - Membership List, 1987-2005 (Box-folder 29A/8)
  - Spur Applications and Reports, 1975-1979 (Box-folder 29A/9)
- National Records, 4
  Records in this series relate to the national chapters of the Spurs. Items include minutes, reports, membership lists, and correspondence.
  - Regional Convention, Region I Minutes (Box 28, Folder 57)
  - Regional Convention, Region VI Minutes (Box 28, Folder 58)
  - Regional Convention, Region IX Minutes (Box 28, Folder 59)
  - Regional Convention, Region XI Minutes (Box 28, Folder 60)
  - Intercollegiate Knights Minutes (Box 28, Folder 61)
  - National Spurs Executive Council Minutes, 1960-1964 (Box 28, Folder 62)
  - National Spurs Executive Council Minutes, 1968-1974 (Box 28, Folder 63)
  - State of the Region Reports, 1973-1979 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - State of the Region Reports (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - State of the Nation Reports, 1972-1977 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - National Spur Convention Reports, 1952-1956 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - National Spur Convention Reports, 1968-1973 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - National Spur Convention Reports, 1966-1985 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - National Spur Convention Reports, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - National Convention Reports, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - National Convention Reports, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - National Convention Reports, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - National Convention Reports, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - National Convention Reports, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - National Convention Reports, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 13-14)
  - National Convention Reports, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - National Convention Reports, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - National Convention Reports, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 17-20)
  - National Convention Reports, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - National Convention Reports, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - National Convention Reports, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - National Convention Reports, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - National Convention Reports, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - National Convention Reports, 1968-1979 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - National Convention Reports, 1971-1988 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - National Convention Reports, 1974-1980 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - National Convention Reports, 1998-2004 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Spur Selection Committee Reports, 1967-1973 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Tapping Committee Reports (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Audit Reports (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Bank Statements, 1965-1984 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Budgets Reports (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Donations Reports (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Insurance Reports (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - By-Laws, 1990-2005 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Constitution, 1929-2005 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Incorporation Reports (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Chapter Histories, 1980-1981 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Chapter Histories, 1982-1986 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Chapter Histories, 1986-1988 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - History of Spurs (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - At Your Service (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Handbooks (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Spur Kit, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Spur Kit, 1964-1967 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Spur Kit, 1965-1976 (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
  - Spur Kit, 1966-1975 (Box 32, Folder 3-4)
  - Spur Kit, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Spur Kit, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 6-7)
  - Spur Kit, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Spur Kit, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Spur Kit, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Spur Kit, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Regional Newsletter (Box 32, Folder 12-16)
  - The Spur, 1931-1960 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - The Spur, 1960-1966 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - The Spur, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - The Spur, 1966-1971 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - The Spur, 1971-1977 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - The Spur, 1977-1982 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - The Spur, 1982-1987 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - The Spur, 2000-2005 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - The Spur-Alumni, 2001-2005 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - The International Spur, 1957-2000 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Region 1, Eastern Montana College (Billings) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Region 1, Montana State University (Bozeman) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Region 1, Northern Montana College (Havre) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Region 1, Rocky Mountain College (Billings) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Region 2, University of Idaho Membership List (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Region 2, Carroll College (Helena) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Region 2, Idaho State (Pocatello) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Region 2, Montana Tech (Butte) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Region 2, University of Missoula (Missoula) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Region 2, West Montana College (Dillon) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Region 3, University of Idaho (Moscow) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Region 3, Washington State University (Pullman) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Region 3, Whitman (Walla Walla) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Region 4, Humbolt State College Membership List (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Region 4, University of Nevada (Reno) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Region 4, Linfield College (McMinnville) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Region 4, Pacific Lutheran University (Tacoma) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Region 4, Pacific University (Forest Grove) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Region 4, Seattle University Membership List (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Region 4, University of Puget Sound (Tacoma) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Region 5, Chico University Membership List (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Region 5, Northern Arizona University (Flagstaff) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Region 5, University of Nevada (Reno) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Region 5, University of Redlands Membership List (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Region 6, Utah State (Logan) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Region 6, Colorado State University (Fort Collins) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Region 6, University of Colorado (Boulder) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Region 6, University of Denver Membership List (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Region 6, University of Northern Colorado (Greeley) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Region 6, University of Wyoming (Laramie) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Region 7, Colorado Women's College (Aurora) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Region 7, Eastern New Mexico (Portales) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Region 7, New Mexico State (Las Cruces) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Region 7, University of New Mexico (Albuquerque) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Region 7, University of Texas (El Paso) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Region 8, University of Arizona (Tucson) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Region 8, California Lutheran College Membership List (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Region 8, BYU (Provo) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Region 8, Arizona State Membership List (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - Region 8, Jamestown College Membership List (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - Region 8, Mary College (U of Mary) (Bismarck) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - Region 8, Moorhead State University (Moorhead) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - Region 8, Northern State University (Aberdeen) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 43)
  - Region 9, Emporia State Membership List (Box 33, Folder 44)
  - Region 9, Fort Hays College (Hays) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 45)
  - Region 9, Kansas State (Manhattan) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 46)
  - Region 11, Wichita State Membership List (Box 33, Folder 47)
  - Region 11, University of Nebraska (Kearney) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 48)
  - Region 11, Butler University Membership List (Box 33, Folder 49)
  - Region 11, Adams State College Membership List (Box 33, Folder 50)
  - Region 11, New Mexico Highlands (Las Vegas, New Mexico) Membership List (Box 33, Folder 51)
  - Region 11, Membership List (Box 33, Folder 52)
  - Region 1 Membership List (Box 33, Folder 53-55)
  - Region 2 Membership List (Box 33, Folder 56-58)
  - Region 3 Membership List (Box 33, Folder 59-60)
  - Region 4 Membership List (Box 33, Folder 61-63)
  - Region 5 Membership List (Box 33, Folder 64-65)
  - Region 6 Membership List (Box 33, Folder 66)
  - Region 7 Membership List (Box 33, Folder 67)
  - Region 7 Membership List (Box 34, Folder 1-2)
  - Region 8 Membership List (Box 34, Folder 3-4)
  - Region 9 Membership List (Box 34, Folder 5-6)
  - Region 10 Membership List (Box 34, Folder 7-8)
  - Region 11 Membership List (Box 34, Folder 9-10)
  - Region 12 Membership List (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Region 19 Membership List (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Addresses (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Convention Attendee List (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Directory (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Chapter Lists (Box 34, Folder 16-17)
  - National Spurs: Montana State Chapter Membership List (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Carroll College, Helena Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Central Washington Street College, Ellensburg Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - University of Arizona Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - University of Alaska Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 22)